Jean Ritchie and George Pickow collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Graphic materials
  - Subseries 9: Projects, festivals, events, and awards
    - During the recording of "High Hills and Mountains," circa 1979 (Box-folder 161/8)
      In Fresno, California. "High Hills and Mountains" was released on Greenhays in 1979.
    - Recording at the Library of Congress, 1950, 1952, 1952, undated (Box-folder 161/9)
    - During the recording of "None But One," circa 1977 (Box-folder 161/10)
      "None But One" was released on Greenhays in 1977.
    - During the recording of "A Time for Singing" (Box-folder 161/11)
    - Residency at Fresno State College, circa 1979 (Box-folder 161/12)
      Jean was a folk artist in residence.
    - Agnes DeMille and Heritage Dance Theatre, 1974, undated (Box-folder 161/13)
    - "America Sings" (Disneyland attraction), 1975 (Box-folder 161/14)
      "America Sings" was an attraction at Disneyland from 1974-1988. Two unrelated slides, dated 1967, are in the folder.
    - "Song-Hunter" (BBC -TV program), 1952 or 1953 (Box-folder 161/15)
      David Attenborough directed or produced Jean's solo on "Song-Hunter."
    - "Camera Three," circa 1959 (Box-folder 161/16)
      A TV series that aired on CBS. Unrelated photos, taken on a boat, are in the folder.
    - "Christmas Revels" (1/2), circa 1970s-2000s (Box-folder 161/17)
      Photos from various years of this production.
    - "Christmas Revels" (2/2), circa 1970s-2000s (Box-folder 162/1)
      See the description for box-folder 161/17.
    - "Folk Song Festival" (Box-folder 162/2)
      Oscar Brand's radio show, on WNYC.
    - "Lyrics and Legends: Ballads" (Box-folder 162/3)
      For the PBS show. Includes photos of Jean, Tristram Coffin, and MacEdward Leach.
    - "Mountain Born: the Jean Ritchie Story," circa 1966 (Box-folder 162/4)
      First broadcast on KET-TV, then PBS. Documentary on Jean's life.
    - "Old Music for New Ears" (Box-folder 162/5)
      An episode of the show, broadcast on KET-TV.
    - "Faces of Creativity," 2010 (Box-folder 162/6)
      Exhibit of George Pickow's photographs, at Port Washington Public Library.
    - "Rope" (theatrical production) (Box-folder 162/7)
      Stage set designed by George Pickow. The show was staged at Cooper Union, New York.
    - "Sing America Sing," 1975 (Box-folder 162/8)
      From the production, staged at the Kennedy Center. Photos unrelated to the subject are also in the folder.
    - "Singing the Moon Up," circa 2000s (Box-folder 162/9)
      Theatrical production in tribute to Jean Ritchie's life and work. Includes a photo from the production, and a photo from George's photography exhibit that accompanied the show.
    - "Songs from the Heart" (Box-folder 162/10)
      Jean and George stand by the theatre poster for the show.
    - Jean on television (Box-folder 162/11)
      Photos of a TV broadcasting a show featuring Jean.
    - "Mountain Stage," March 15, 1992 (Box-folder 162/12)
      Radio show broadcast on West Virginia Public Radio.
    - "Wide Wide World," 1955 (Box-folder 162/13)
      Television program; this episode was recorded (at least in part) in Greensboro, South Carolina.
    - Japan tour (Box-folder 162/14)
      Photos from Jean's 1978 tour of Japan.
    - Workshop at Keuka College, New York, 1948 (Box-folder 162/15)
  - Subseries 10: Artists and musicians
    Includes other individuals of note, such as politicians and leaders.
    - Bob Abramson (Box-folder 162/16)
    - Irving Amen (Box-folder 162/17)
      Woodcarver
    - George Armstrong (Box-folder 162/18)
      2 frames, young man playing autoharp, 2 frames, immediate Pickow family
    - Louis Armstrong, 1964 (Box-folder 162/19)
      Recording session
    - Clarence (Tom) Ashley and band (Box-folder 162/20)
    - Joan Baez (Box-folder 163/1)
      Performing
    - Margaret Barry and Michael Gorman (Box-folder 163/2)
    - David Ben-Gurion (Box-folder 163/3)
    - Thomas Hart Benton (Box-folder 163/4)
    - Elmer Bernstein (Box-folder 163/5)
    - Theodore Bikel (Box-folder 163/6)
    - Ellie and Gene Bluestein (Box-folder 163/7)
    - Doc Boggs and wife (Box-folder 163/8)
    - Bill Bonyun (Box-folder 163/9)
    - Boone, Daniel (VII) (Box-folder 163/10)
      Welder
    - Oscar Brand (1/3) (Box-folder 163/11)
      Includes publicity photos and performance photos.
    - Oscar Brand (2/3) (Box-folder 163/12)
      See the description for box-folder 163/11.
    - Oscar Brand (3/3) (Box-folder 163/13)
    - David Burliuk (Box-folder 163/14)
    - Isla Cameron (Box-folder 163/15)
    - Jon Carrol (Box-folder 163/16)
    - Mother Maybelle Carter (Box-folder 163/17)
    - Chad Mitchell Trio, circa 1965-1966 (Box-folder 163/18)
      John Denver appears at center.
    - Goingback "G.B." Chiltoskey (Box-folder 163/19)
      Folk Artist; Cherokee, NC
    - Memorial concert for Paddy Clancy (Box-folder 163/20)
    - Sibyl Clarke (Box-folder 163/21)
    - Paul Clayton (Box-folder 163/22)
    - Tristram Coffin (Box-folder 163/23)
    - John Cohen (Box-folder 163/24)
    - William Cohen and Dolores Cohen (Box-folder 163/25)
    - Judy Collins (Box-folder 164/1)
      Performing and in studio
    - Shirley Collins (Box-folder 164/2)
    - Columbian Squires (Box-folder 164/3)
    - Coon Creek Girls (Box-folder 164/4)
      Publicity photo
    - Elizabeth Cronin (Box-folder 164/5)
      and nephew Daivah Cronin and family
    - Merce Cunningham (Box-folder 164/6)
      Dancing
    - Agnes DeMille (Box-folder 164/7)
    - Era Desca (Box-folder 164/8)
      Publicity photos
    - Lotus Dickey (Box-folder 164/9)
      Casual photo with the Pickows
    - Ben Dinsimore (Box-folder 164/10)
      Playing dulcimer
    - Edie Doughty (Box-folder 164/11)
      Group photo, labeled on back
    - Bob Dylan (Box-folder 164/12)
      Performing at Newport
    - Ramblin' Jack Elliot (Box-folder 164/13)
      Playing in Washington Square Park
    - Duncan Emrich (Box-folder 164/14)
      With Jean Ritchie in studio
    - Seamus Ennis (Box-folder 164/15)
      Posed with Jean Ritchie and photos of Robert Dinsmore
    - Richard Farina, 1965 (Box-folder 164/16)
      Richard Farina and Jean onstage together.
    - Sam Fisher (Box-folder 164/17)
    - Folger Consort with Scott Riess (Box-folder 164/18)
      Scott Riess plays recorder.
    - Edith Folke (Box-folder 164/19)
    - May Gadd (Box-folder 164/20)
    - Cynthia Gooding (Box-folder 164/21)
    - Sid Gordon (Box-folder 164/22)
    - Yvonne Gregory (Box-folder 165/1)
    - Chaim Gross (Box-folder 165/2)
    - Harry and Diane Guggenheim (Box-folder 165/3)
    - Woody Guthrie, circa 1948 (Box-folder 165/4)
      Jean with Woody Guthrie, Pete Seeger, and Fred Hellerman in the studio, in New York City. Photos by Raymond Ross.
    - Richard Hagopian (Box-folder 165/5)
    - Jane Hair (Box-folder 165/6)
    - Diane Hamilton (Box-folder 165/7)
    - David Hammond (Box-folder 165/8)
    - Emmylou Harris (Box-folder 165/9)
    - John Hartford (Box-folder 165/10)
    - Joe Heaney (Box-folder 165/11)
    - John Herald (Box-folder 165/12)
    - Sam Hinton (Box-folder 165/13)
    - Hans Hoffman (Box-folder 165/14)
      Artist
    - Edward Hopper (Box-folder 165/15)
    - Mississippi John Hurt (Box-folder 165/16)
    - Skip James (Box-folder 165/17)
    - Bessie Jones; Georgia Sea Island Singers (Box-folder 165/18)
    - Grandpa Jones (Box-folder 165/19)
      1 slide
    - Tom Jones (Box-folder 165/20)
    - Peter Kennedy (Box-folder 165/21)
    - Martin Luther King (Box-folder 165/22)
      Photos by Arthur F. Smith, Jr.
    - Chuck Klein (Box-folder 165/23)
    - Frank Kleinholz (Box-folder 165/24)
    - Spider Ray Koerner (Box-folder 165/25)
      Alone, and with the group Koerner, Ray and Glover
    - Howard Koslow, 1982 (Box-folder 165/26)
    - Carol Langstaff (Box-folder 165/27)
    - Leadbelly (Huddie Ledbetter) (Box-folder 165/28)
    - Hyman, Dick (Box-folder 166/1)
    - Ann Landers, circa 1959 (Box-folder 166/2)
      Columnist Ann Landers and her daughter, in New York, NY
    - MacEdward Leach (Box-folder 166/3)
      Leach interviews a Pennsylvania storyteller.
    - Lily May Ledford (Box-folder 166/4)
    - Lorraine Lee (Box-folder 166/5)
    - Mance Lipscomb (Box-folder 166/6)
    - Alan Lomax (Box-folder 166/7)
      Includes post-it notes in Jean Ritchie's handwriting with descriptive material
    - Jimmy MacBeath (Box-folder 166/8)
    - Jacqueline MacDonald (Box-folder 166/9)
      Performed and recorded with Bridie O'Donnell under the name Jacqui and Bridie.
    - Ewan MacColl (Box-folder 166/10)
    - Tommy Makem (Box-folder 166/11)
    - The Mamas and the Papas (Box-folder 166/12)
      Composite transparencies
    - Jayne Mansfield and Mickey Hargitay (Box-folder 166/13)
    - Marais and Miranda (Box-folder 166/14)
    - Reginald Marsh (Box-folder 166/15)
    - Kathy Mattea (Box-folder 166/16)
    - Ed McCurdy (Box-folder 166/17)
    - John McCutcheon (Box-folder 166/18)
    - Linda McKay (Box-folder 166/19)
    - Raymond McLain (Box-folder 166/20)
      Wedding of his daughter, Ruth.
    - McPeakes (Box-folder 166/21)
    - Bill Monroe (Box-folder 166/22)
    - Al Moss (Box-folder 166/23)
      At Camp Unity. Al Moss was married to Laura Duncan (singer).
    - New Lost City Ramblers (Box-folder 166/24)
    - John Jacob Niles (Box-folder 166/25)
    - Phil Ochs (Box-folder 167/1)
    - Daihb O'Cronin (Box-folder 167/2)
      Professor.
    - Sally Olds (Box-folder 167/3)
    - Brendan O'Malley (Box-folder 167/4)
    - The Patons (Box-folder 167/5)
    - Faith Petrie (Box-folder 167/6)
    - Jon Pickow (Box-folder 167/7)
    - Peter Pickow, 1950 (Box-folder 167/8)
    - Pickow-Ritchie wedding (Box-folder 167/9)
      Jean Ritchie and George Pickow were married on September 29, 1950, in Washington, D.C., at the Seventh Baptist Church. See box-folder 136/7.
    - Frank Proffitt (Box-folder 167/10)
      Proffitt singing to friends.
    - John Raitt (Box-folder 167/11)
    - John Renbourne (Box-folder 167/12)
    - Bill Rew, circa 1953 (Box-folder 167/13)
      Jean Ritchie recorded his performance of "Barbara Allen."
    - Ritchie family (1/2) (Box-folder 167/14)
      Family photos, including Jean as a teenager.
    - Ritchie family (2/2) (Box-folder 167/15)
      Family photos, primarily with Jean and George's family.
    - Jean Ritchie and Oscar Brand (Box-folder 167/16)
    - Jean Ritchie with other artists (Box-folder 167/17)
      Includes Pete Seeger, Judy Collins, and others.
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (1/19) (Box-folder 168/1)
      Includes posed and unposed photos.
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (2/19) (Box-folder 168/2)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (3/19) (Box-folder 168/3)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (4/19) (Box-folder 168/4)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (5/19) (Box-folder 168/5)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (6/19) (Box-folder 169/1)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (7/19) (Box-folder 169/2)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (8/19) (Box-folder 169/3)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (9/19) (Box-folder 169/4)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (10/19) (Box-folder 169/5)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (11/19) (Box-folder 169/6)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (12/19) (Box-folder 170/1)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (13/19) (Box-folder 170/2)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (14/19) (Box-folder 170/3)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (15/19) (Box-folder 170/4)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (16/19) (Box-folder 170/5)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (17/19) (Box-folder 170/6)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (18/19) (Box-folder 170/7)
    - Jean Ritchie - publicity photos (19/19) (Box-folder 170/8)
    - Ritter and Lerner (Box-folder 171/1)
    - Robin Roberts, 1954 (Box-folder 171/2)
      Studio Photos
    - Jeannie Robertson (Box-folder 171/3)
    - Buffy Sainte-Marie (Box-folder 171/4)
    - Carl Sandburg (1/3) (Box-folder 171/5)
    - Carl Sandburg (2/3) (Box-folder 171/6)
    - Carl Sandburg (3/3) (Box-folder 171/7)
    - Avery Schreiber (Box-folder 171/8)
    - Ivey Scott (Box-folder 171/9)
    - Mike Seeger (Box-folder 171/10)
    - The Seegers (Box-folder 171/11)
    - Pete Seeger (Box-folder 171/12)
    - Rick Skaggs (Box-folder 171/13)
    - Pamela Smith (Box-folder 171/14)
    - Ralph Smith (Box-folder 171/15)
    - Rosalie Sorrels (Box-folder 172/1)
    - Moses Soyer (Box-folder 172/2)
    - Victoria Spivey (Box-folder 172/3)
    - Ellen Stekert (Box-folder 172/4)
    - James Still (Box-folder 172/5)
    - David Stone (Box-folder 172/6)
    - William Howard Taft III, circa 1953 (Box-folder 172/7)
      U.S. Ambassador to Ireland (1953-1957) and grandson of the U.S. president.
    - Arthur J. "Putt" Telfer (Box-folder 172/8)
      Noted photographer who documented life in Cooperstown, New York.
    - Sonny Terry and Brownie McGhee (Box-folder 172/9)
    - Big Mama Thornton (Box-folder 172/10)
    - Happy and Artie Traum (Box-folder 172/11)
    - Mary Travers (Box-folder 172/12)
    - Merle Travis (Box-folder 172/13)
    - Ralph Vaughn Williams (Box-folder 172/14)
    - Frank Warner (Box-folder 172/15)
      Includes shots in camphouse at Pinewoods leading a song.
    - Doc Watson (Box-folder 172/16)
    - Elaine Weissman (Box-folder 172/17)
      concert producer
    - Dennis Wharton (Box-folder 172/18)
      Cartoonist
    - Jane White (Box-folder 172/19)
    - Josh White (Box-folder 172/20)
    - White, Walter and Jane (daughter, actress) (Box-folder 172/21)
    - Charles Willis and Dot Willis (Box-folder 173/1)
    - Hally Wood (Box-folder 173/2)
    - Russell Wortley (Box-folder 173/3)
    - Denys Wortman (Box-folder 173/4)
    - Young Tradition, The (Box-folder 173/5)
      1960s-era British folk group, comprised of Peter Bellamy, Arielle Heather Wood, and Royston Wood.
  - Subseries 11: Musicians, artists, performers, and authors
    - Artists (1/4) (Box-folder 173/6)
      Musical artists and artists who create physical objects.
    - Artists (2/4) (Box-folder 173/7)
      See the description for box-folder 173/6.
    - Artists (3/4) (Box-folder 173/8)
    - Artists (4/4) (Box-folder 173/9)
    - Musicians (1/3) (Box-folder 173/10)
    - Musicians (2/3) (Box-folder 173/11)
    - Musicians (3/3) (Box-folder 174/1)
    - Performers (1/3) (Box-folder 174/2)
    - Performers (2/3) (Box-folder 174/3)
    - Performers (3/3) (Box-folder 174/4)
    - Musicians, artists, and authors (Box-folder 174/5)
  - Subseries 12: Subjects
    George's photographs often accompanied magazine articles; a number of the photos in this subseries represent this work.
    - Agriculture (Box-folder 174/6)
      Produce, animals in pens, and related subjects.
    - Animal Hospital (Box-folder 174/7)
      Photos of dogs in bandages being tended to (no actual injuries are evident).
    - Animals (Box-folder 175/1)
      Cats, dogs, horses, birds, stuffed animals, etc.
    - Antiques (Box-folder 175/2)
      Photos inside an antique store.
    - Arts (1/3) (Box-folder 175/3)
      Various forms of art, artists at work, and artists with their work. Also includes children's art.
    - Arts (2/3) (Box-folder 175/4)
      See the description for box-folder 175/3.
    - Arts (3/3) (Box-folder 175/5)
    - Dance (1/2) (Box-folder 175/6)
      Photos of dancers in motion and at rest; primarily modern dance.
    - Dance (2/2) (Box-folder 176/1)
      See the description for box-folder 175/6.
    - Exotic dance (Box-folder 176/2)
    - George Pickow (Box-folder 176/3)
      Photos of paintings and sculptures, photos of George at work, and postcards from some of George's photo exhibits.
    - Mobiles (1/2) (Box-folder 176/4)
      Photos of mobiles (suspended sculptures) being made, and on display.
    - Mobiles (2/2) (Box-folder 176/5)
      See the description for box-folder 176/4.
    - Music (Box-folder 177/1)
      Orchestra rehearsals and a performance.
    - Performing (Box-folder 177/2)
      Stage, circus, and cabaret performers.
    - Silk screen artist (Box-folder 177/3)
      Stages of silk screen art production.
    - Theatrical (Box-folder 177/4)
      Stage plays
    - Woodcuts (Box-folder 177/5)
      Irving Amen is the featured artist.
    - Transportation (Box-folder 177/6)
      Boats, ships, airplanes, pollution, and related subjects.
    - Education (Box-folder 177/7)
      School children in various educational settings.
    - Effects (Box-folder 177/8)
      Special effects and naturally-occuring effects.
    - American history (1/9) (Box-folder 178/1)
      Photos of art, other photos, architecture, signs, cowboys, photos used for events, the events themselves, landscapes, portraits of Native American individuals (may be photos Curtis photos,
    - American history (2/9) (Box-folder 178/2)
      See the description for box-folder 178/1.
    - American history (3/9) (Box-folder 178/3)
    - American history (4/9) (Box-folder 178/4)
    - American history (5/9) (Box-folder 179/1)
    - American history (6/9) (Box-folder 179/2)
    - American history (7/9) (Box-folder 179/3)
    - American history (8/9) (Box-folder 179/4)
    - American history (9/9) (Box-folder 180/1)
    - Holidays—Christmas (Box-folder 180/2)
      Stock photos
    - Holidays—Jewish (Box-folder 180/3)
      Photos of schoolchildren, preparing for a Purim parade, making hamentaschen, and photos of menorahs.
    - Industry—Eastern Airlines flight attendants (Box-folder 180/4)
      Photos of flight attendants on the job and preparing for work.
    - Industry (1/3) (Box-folder 180/5)
      Stock photos of blue collar workers on the job.
    - Industry (2/3) (Box-folder 180/6)
      See the description for box-folder 180/5.
    - Industry (3/3) (Box-folder 180/7)
    - Industry - plaster saints factory (Box-folder 181/1)
      The production of plaster figurines of saints.
    - Industry - printing (Box-folder 181/2)
      Photos of the printing process.
    - Industry - WMCA (radio station) (Box-folder 181/3)
      Photos of broadcasters and the audience.
    - Interiors (Box-folder 181/4)
      Interiors of public spaces. Includes some exterior shots.
    - Libraries (Box-folder 181/5)
      Includes photos of what seems to be a person signing.
    - Medieval restaurant (Box-folder 181/6)
      Dining and entertainment in a restaurant intended to recreate the medieval dining experience.
    - Model - home (Box-folder 181/7)
      One photo of a model-sized home under construction.
    - Log homes (Box-folder 181/8)
      Various structures.
    - Model railroad (Box-folder 181/9)
      Photos of the rainroad and its workings.
    - Models - bodybuilders (Box-folder 181/10)
      Most photos are of male bodybuilders, photographed outdoors.
    - Models - infants and children (1/2) (Box-folder 181/11)
      Includes mostly stock photos of infants and children.
    - Models - infants and children (2/2) (Box-folder 181/12)
      See the description for box-folder 181/11.
    - Models - fashion (1/4) (Box-folder 182/1)
      High fashion, swimsuit, and casual wear, in a variety of settings.
    - Models - fashion (2/4) (Box-folder 182/2)
      See the description for box-folder 182/1.
    - Models - fashion (3/4) (Box-folder 182/3)
    - Models - fashion (4/4) (Box-folder 182/4)
    - Models - general (1/10) (Box-folder 182/5)
      Models in a variety of settings.
    - Models - general (2/10) (Box-folder 182/6)
      See the description for box-folder 182/5.
    - Models - general (3/10) (Box-folder 183/1)
    - Models - general (4/10) (Box-folder 183/2)
    - Models - general (5/10) (Box-folder 183/3)
    - Models - general (6/10) (Box-folder 183/4)
    - Models - general (7/10) (Box-folder 183/5)
    - Models - general (8/10) (Box-folder 183/6)
    - Models - general (9/10) (Box-folder 184/1)
    - Models - general (10/10) (Box-folder 184/2)
    - Models - nude (Box-folder 184/3)
    - Models - skiing (Box-folder 184/4)
    - Models - teenage (Box-folder 184/5)
    - Models - underwater (Box-folder 184/6)
    - Models - beach and water sports (Box-folder 184/7)
    - Musical instruments (1/5) (Box-folder 184/8)
      Photos of instruments (especially brass instruments and dulcimers), including close-ups and artistic renderings using special effects.
    - Musical instruments (2/5) (Box-folder 185/1)
      See the description for box-folder 184/8.
    - Musical instruments (3/5) (Box-folder 185/2)
    - Musical instruments (4/5) (Box-folder 185/3)
    - Musical instruments (5/5) (Box-folder 185/4)
    - Objects (1/3) (Box-folder 185/5)
      Stock photographs of everyday and ornamental objects, as well as photos intended for magazines featuring fictional and non-fictional detective stories.
    - Objects (2/3) (Box-folder 185/6)
      See the description for box-folder 185/5.
    - Objects (3/3) (Box-folder 185/7)
    - Plants, trees, and flowers (Box-folder 186/1)
    - Scenic - buildings (Box-folder 186/2)
    - Scenic (1/3) (Box-folder 186/3)
      A compilation of images, many of which are from among other subject categories in this collection. Subjects include mountains, sunsets, plants, landscapes, structures, autumn foliage, and Jean in concert.
    - Scenic (2/3) (Box-folder 186/4)
      See the description for box-folder 186/3.
    - Scenic - USA and abroad (1/2) (Box-folder 186/5)
    - Scenic - USA and abroad (2/2) (Box-folder 186/6)
    - Science - astronomy (Box-folder 186/7)
      Photos of the earth, a moon landing with an astronaut and a US flag, and the moon module.
    - Science - chemistry (Box-folder 186/8)
      Photos of a man using lab equipment.
    - Science - dentistry (Box-folder 186/9)
      Photos of a dentist at work.
    - Science - prenatal and neonatal (Box-folder 186/10)
    - Science - medicine (Box-folder 187/1)
      Photos of doctors and nurses, medical settings, x-rays, and related subjects.
    - Sports (Box-folder 187/2)
      Weightlifting, basketball, hockey, tennis, golf, football, baseball, and other sports.
    - Children (Box-folder 187/3)
      Children at play and in school, and infants being fed.
    - Swissair (Box-folder 187/4)
      Photos of daily business operations at Swissair.
    - Voodoo (Box-folder 187/5)
      Photos of a ceremony and dancers. Unrelated photos are also in the folder.
    - Women who work on Wall Street (Box-folder 187/6)
      Contact photos of women who work on Wall Street.
    - Miscellaneous women (Box-folder 187/7)
      Copies of photos from other folders in this collection.
    - Zoology (Box-folder 187/8)
      Animals and people. Includes performing animals.
    - For Three Lions (Box-folder 187/9)
      Work done for the Three Lions photo agency. Subjects and content include occupations and portraits.
    - Very early transparencies (Box-folder 187/10)
      Various subjects, which appear in other folders in this collection.
    - Early prints (Box-folder 187/11)
      See the description for box-folder 187/10.
    - Color transparencies (Box-folder 188/1)
    - Contacts without negatives (1/2) (Box-folder 188/2)
    - Contacts without negatives (2/2) (Box-folder 188/3)
    - Miscellaneous photos (Box-folder 188/4)
      See the description for box-folder 187/10. Includes family photos from scrapbook pages.
    - Unidentified scenes (Box-folder 188/5)
      A group of photos for undetermined subjects categories. Received thus from the donor.
  - Subseries 13: Subjects (2013 accrual)
    See scope and content note for Subseries 12.
    - Dance (1/2) (Box-folder 188/6)
      Folk dance and related activities.
    - Dance (2/2) (Box-folder 188/7)
      See the description for box-folder 188/6.
    - Folk dance (Box-folder 189/1)
      Photos and negatives sent by George Pickow to Mr. W.W. Lowen. Photos of folk dance in various countries.
    - Dogs (1/2) (Box-folder 189/2)